[
    {
      "level": 1,
      "question": "What is the capital of France?",
      "options": [
        "London",
        "Berlin",
        "Paris",
        "Madrid"
      ],
      "correct": 2,
      "prize": 100
    },
    {
      "level": 2,
      "question": "Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
      "options": [
        "Venus",
        "Mars", 
        "Jupiter",
        "Saturn"
      ],
      "correct": 1,
      "prize": 200
    },
    {
        "level": 3,
        "question": "Who discovered America?",
        "options":[
            "Napolean",
            "Columbus",
            "Washington",
            "Smith"
        ],
        "correct": 1,
        "prize": 300
    },
    {
        "level": 4,
        "question": "Which country is home to the iconic Taj Mahal?",
        "options":[
            "Pakistan",
            "Bangladesh",
            "India",
            "Bhutan"
        ],
        "correct": 2,
        "prize": 500
    },
    {
        "level": 5,
        "question": "The hammer and sickle is one of the most recognisable symbols of which political ideology?",
        "options":[
            "Communism",
            "Liberalism",
            "Conversatism",
            "Republicanism"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "prize": 1000
    },
    {
        "level": 6,
        "question": "In the bible which disciple of Jesus was crucified upside down in 64 CE?",
        "options":[
            "Saint john",
            "Bartholomew",
            "Simon Peter",
            "Judas Iscariot"
        ],
        "correct": 2,
        "prize": 2000
    },
    {
        "level": 7,
        "question": "Which charater said this quote 'One shall stand, One shall fall'in a movie?",
        "options":[
            "Julius Ceaser",
            "Alexander the great",
            "Leonidas",
            "Optimus Prime"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "prize": 4000
    },
    {
        "level": 8,
        "question": "What does 'loquacious' mean?",
        "options":[
            "Chatty",
            "Shy",
            "Angry",
            "Beautiful"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "prize": 8000
    },
    {
        "level": 9,
        "question": "What British inventor is credited for developing the concept of the world's first programmable computer, the Analytical Engine, in the 1830s?",
        "options":[
            "Alan Turing",
            "Ada Lovelace",
            "Charles Babbage",
            "John von Neumann"
        ],
        "correct": 2,
        "prize": 16000
    },
    {
        "level": 10,
        "question": "Which actor played the 11th Doctor in Doctor Who?",
        "options":[
            "David Tennant",
            "Robert Downey Jr.",
            "Math Smith",
            "Jack Black"
        ],
        "correct": 2,
        "prize": 32000
    },
    {
        "level": 10,
        "question": "What is the real name of the guitarist known as Slash, famous for his work with Guns N' Roses?",
        "options":[
            "Angus Young",
            "Saul Hudson",
            "David Howell Evans",
            "Steve Hackett"
        ],
        "correct": 1,
        "prize": 32000
    },
    {
        "level": 11,
        "question": "Which of these characters did not appear in Super Smash Bros Ultimate?",
        "options":[
            "Waluigi",
            "Mario",
            "Sonic the Hedgehog",
            "Wii Fit Trainer"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "prize": 64000
    },
    {
        "level": 11,
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist in the first Assassin's creed game in 2007?",
        "options":[
            "Edward Kenway",
            "Desmond Miles",
            "Ezio Auditore da Firenze",
            "Connor"
        ],
        "correct": 1,
        "prize": 64000
    },
    {
        "level": 12,
        "question": "The Celiac Ganglia are nerve bundles located in __________ as a part of teh autonomic nervous system that is responsible for innervating the digestive tract.",
        "options":[
            "Upper Abdomen",
            "Lower Abdomen",
            "Spine",
            "Kidney"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "prize": 125000
    },
    {
        "level": 13,
        "question": "Which programming language was originally called 'Oak'?",
        "options":[
            "Ruby",
            "C++",
            "Java",
            "Python"
        ],
        "correct": 2,
        "prize": 250000
    },
     {
        "level": 14,
        "question": "Lionel Messi scored his first Champions League goal against which team?",
        "options":[
            "Panathinaikos",
            "Chelsea",
            "Shakhtar Donetsk",
            "Werder Bremen"
        ],
        "correct": 3,
        "prize": 500000
    },
    {
        "level": 15,
        "question": "What is the name of the river in the Underworld that, according to some sources, makes those who drink from it forget their past lives?",
        "options":[
            "Styx",
            "Lethe",
            "Acheron",
            "Phlegethon"
        ],
        "correct": 0,
        "prize": 1000000
    }
    
  ]
  
